<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>thepersonever rss!!</title>
<link>https://thepersonever.net/</link>
<description>a nekoweb rss feed... thing. remember 2 clear ur cache!!</description>

<item>
<title>something more to say, actually</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 03:36:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.net/randomerjunk/art</link>
<guid isPermaLink='false'>art2024</guid>
<description>i finally got around to adding all my 2024 traditional drawings to the art page! a lot of my digital art has been in animations so i don't have a lot for the digital 2024 section...
make sure to scroll to the bottom of the drawings if you want to look at all of them in chronological order!
i suck at drawing</description>
</item>	

<item>
<title>new albums on the cd page! </title>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:51:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.net/randomerjunk/cds</link>
<guid isPermaLink='false'>cds1</guid>
<description>not much more to say... i also fixed some typos though :D</description>
</item>	

<item>
<title>mobile updates + complaining about text limit</title>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 15:44:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.net/nekotwt.xml</link>
<guid isPermaLink='false'>mobile1</guid>
<description>hi! i updated parts of my site recently to make it more mobile-friendly. the main five TPE pages, and all of xDx3xP are now a lot easier to browse on vertical devices! i'm still working on random junk though, so expect that to be updated a little later &lt;/3
i also found out yesterday that nekoweb TRIES to cap its rss feeds' length so that text doesn't overflow. it doesn't really do a good job at it though, since text still overflows a lot on less-wide screens :/ 
you can click on this post to go to my rss feed! so that you can put it in a better rss reader!!! but i'll still try to keep my rss posts shorter from now on. try.</description>
</item>	

<item>
<title>more small news</title>
<pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:18:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.net/flashes/pikitorytest</link>
<guid isPermaLink='false'>pikitoryschool2</guid>
<description>hey! not much to report on today. brought my actual laptop to school though!!! ...pikitory is going at a steady 1 page/panel per day, as per usual, but i'm drawing in flash now! i'm most likely gonna outline my  process of turning vector drawings into clean sprites in the future, but you'll just have to WOOONDDEEERRRRR for now :3c
the url for this page leads to the old pikitory flash i made in like... 2023? early 2024? that i've largely replaced everything for-only the scenerio and song remains for the new flash. this version's audio is also unsynced, due to being made in HTML5. sorry, but adobe animate fucking sucks!</description>
</item>	

<item>
<title>working on pikitory again</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:38:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.net/</link>
<guid isPermaLink='false'>pikitoryschool</guid>
<description>hey! im working on the absolute pikitory amv that ive had in my head for a while now. i'm also making it in as3 now, as i've learned that HTML5 just... isn't there yet for animations
i took a break from the amv a while ago due to people stress... i'm currently experiencing people stress again. send help
technically im actually still in school right now but who cares</description>
</item>	

<item>
<title>postbox done!</title>
<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 23:31:04 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.net/</link>
<guid isPermaLink='false'>postboxdone</guid>
<description>yeah that's really all i have. i hope it looks good :p</description>
</item>	

<item>
<title>okay cool. good. nice.</title>
<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 21:23:00 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3</guid>
<link>https://thepersonever.net/tools/rss</link>
<description>okay figured it out. nekoweb wants two articles until it starts posting on the feed. okay.
	also i moved it to https://thepersonever.net/tools/rss if you want to use my shitty item generator</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>test part 2</title>
<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 20:56:03 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2</guid>
<link>https://thepersonever.net/</link>
<description>ugh. gotta set up guid on the rssgen page. https://psfla.net/tests/rss.html btw</description>
</item>	

<item>
<title>woohoo nekotests</title>
<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 19:31:07 GMT</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">1</guid>
<link>https://thepersonever.net/</link>
<description>testing? testing???... is this thing on?
i made a webpage just for this if this doesn't work i'll</description>
</item>	

</channel>
</rss>
