<rss version="2.0">    
<channel>
<title>thepersonever's blog??</title>

<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/</link>
<description>rose's existence</description>
<category>Homepage</category>
<language>en-us</language>
<image>
<url>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/images/blogicon.png</url>
<title>thepersonever's blog :(</title>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org</link>
</image>

<!-- <item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> name
    </title>
  <pubDate>12 14 2022 8:22 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
<p>hi
</p>
  
</description>
</item> -->

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> ALERT...
    </title>
  <pubDate>11 30 2023</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
<p>this rss feed is DEPRECATED! it will no longer recive updates.
<br /> please refer to either <a href="https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html">the website's original blog page</a> or <a href="https://www.tumblr.com/thepersonever-site-updates/">the new update blog on tumblr</a>. the tumblr updates will be shorter, but will also include blog posts when written. 
</p>
  
</description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> whats summer? how does it taste?
    </title>
  <pubDate>8 24 2023</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
<p> i neglected this site for like a month i am SUCH a good parent :3
<br /> anyways
<br /> i got an actual computer!!! instead of like!!! having a laptop without a battery or monitor!!!!
<br /> so now i can like upgrade it slowly and have it be actually able to play games :D 
<br /> uh i also played pikmin 4 this summer. almost finished that one cave thats in the post game hub... the final floor is trying to stab me in the gut though
<br /> i also just finished problem sleuth. its great i love it 
<br /> and uh!!! um!!!! i got my twitter account suspended :D 
<br /> sadly i made a new one so im still in hell
<br /> um i also found a sarcophagus under my shed i promise
<br /> anyways uh. bye :P 
</p>
  
</description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> im a responsible web dev
    </title>
  <pubDate>6 27 2023 </pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
<p>uh!!! hello
<br />i TOLD myself i would continue updating my site even past the end of school, and, well,
<br />you can see how well that turned out.
<br />i made another twitter account so ive been spending most of my time there??? it really just makes me anxious but. its the only way i know how to communicate with people so >_>
<br />uh. in terms of more creative-y stuff
<br />ive started using flstudio instead of lmms!! its a lot better at copy and paste stuff and is SO better when using samples but. soundfonts dont sound as good as they should sometimes :(
<br />ive also started drawing for an mspfa that a friend wrote! it doesnt look that good and it doesnt have an actual title yet but. yk ^_^
<br />ive also been working on a Really Bad animation for lawnmower. but. i started it in flash without realizing the avi encoding is broken for flash 10 :( so unless you wanna download a swf file... and flash player 10...
<br />
<br />im probably not gonna host the mspfa on thepersonever even once it gets a name, since its not just some silly thing im doing by myself... but ill almost definitely put a thing at home saying "hey look at this i worked on this!!!" once its ready to be. viewed.
<br />
<br />im sorry this blog post is so short :(
</p>
</description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> crocs and javascript
    </title>
  <pubDate>5 10 2023</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
<p> well uh. hi
<br />ive been inclined to write another one of these things !! half because im still forever out of ideas, half because i like. just cant work on my website right now. even though i want to
<br />so!!!! im just writing another blog post... aha
<br />i have like. a few things to talk about... first thing is that!! i have become a homestuck
<br />yipperydoodles i know what an alteria and a beforus is thats so insane im so cool totally i have unearthed something that no one else as uncovered before Anyways
<br />crocs. those <a href='https://thepersonever.neocities.org/images/crocs.jpeg'>green shoes</a>
<br />those things. i have a pair now
<br />theyre actually neon green... but they were the only green they had so :P 
<br />apparently some people think theyre comfy??? i mean they are made out of foam
<br />
<br /> but they have <a href='https://thepersonever.neocities.org/images/OW.png'>SPIKES </a>
<br /> seriously they hurt. :( 
<br /> im sure it hurts less once youve gotten used to how they feel but!!! i just got mine yesterday theyre still like. the soles are still not super dirty
<br /> also they make your feet stink... i can vaguely smell rotten cabbage from my Repugnant Appendages aka my feet
<br /> so?? why am i wearing crocs ??????
<br /> its becauwse apparently ive been abusing my toe :( i dont think itd be ungross to say more than that
<br /> ALSO - i went on crocs.com because it was on my shoe right
<br /> well!! apparently ruffle likes to think that crocs.com is a flash site
<br /> so my browser just showed a blank page when i went to the website...
<br /> i used inspect element to see if the page was actually empty, and then i saw a ruffle thing?? so i turned off ruffle for a bit and then. the site worked! aha
<br />anyways, javascript!!1! ive gotten slightly better at it
<br /> mainly because i know what a function is now. i can finally make a game if i feel so inclined to do so ^_^
<br /> anddd i have nothing else to talk about!! i mean
<br /> this might be the first cross platform blog thing i post. if im not lazy
<br /> i dont count on myself to not be lazy, but i also dont count her to be lazy either!! shrodinger’s lazy
<br /> anyways yeah byebye 
<br /> have a good!!! whatever your having!!!!
</p>
  
</description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> just an update...
    </title>
  <pubDate>4 13 2023</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  

<p> uh hi!! hello hi!!!! im hi and hello
<br /> do you ever just explode an imploding exodus? no? well me neither
<br /> what the Heck is an exodus???? anywyas
<br /> ive! been uh. consuming media yeah
<br /> uh!!!! heres like sokme games ive been playing!!! and brief summaries 
<br /> i played!!!!
<br /> starfox 64 - its like starfox snes but i can actually beat the first stage. its also got really good music too and its fun once you play it for like 4 hours. how are you supposed to beat andross ive gotten chewed up so much its so
<br /> warriors (yeah) - heckingf!!!!!! ist like if books were about cats and the cats were personified and!!! if you didnt recognise anything. they also have there own mini language based off of english 
<br /> pikmin two but on a crt - it looks hecking!!!! really good. like. it was meant for a more blurry display or something :^] 
<br /> i actually beat it!!!! like a week and a half ago but still!!!
<br /> pikmin 3 wii u !! i think i like this version more that the switch one... like u can set up the gamepad as like a second monitor and become able to check every single pikmin ever sprouted in your current save basically??? also switching captains is the same every time. ALSO also i like the camera and stuff more. and the controls aha. like. 
<br /> pikmin one and two’s wii ports didnt really click all that well for me... like... this series was made for the pointer, but not these games. but!!! pikmin 3 was made with the pointer in mind so it feels like right!!!! and good!!! and hggh
<br /> anyways!!!!! thats it. sorry it was so short :( 
<br />beybey

<br />
<br /> ive also started reading livingroomconcealed. yeah im one of “those people” :]
</p>

</description>
</item>


<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> javascript and websites and sitewebs
    </title>
  <pubDate>3 24 2023 1:23 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
<p>uh. hi!!!!
<br />i haven't been posting too many blogs because. i keep forgetting
<br />its been like what... almost 3 months? idk
<br />anyways, 
<br />heres stuff that uh. happened!!!!
<br />-booo my school laptop’s password got changed
<br />-i installed linux mint on the SEROUS XP LAPTOP
<br />-ive been websiteing. really hard. yeah
<br />-drawing!!! has happened a lot!!!! i keep forgetting to update the art part of my site tho
<br />-i picked up transformice the mice that transform
<br />-uh. uhh um uh
<br />yeah! uh! time to elaborate on! things! post meat
<br />my laptop’s password was uh. changed. so i cant work on stuff in class anymore :( thats it
<br />
<br />uh!!! linux amiright!!!!! i wanted something more modern on my laptop... but uh... it was made in the vista era,, so that kinda limits what i can put on it... i opted for the last 32 bit release of linux mint xfce :P
<br />its!!! alright. i have to do modprobe b43 to get the wireless to work tho... and i couldnt figure out how to get it to run at startup sooooo Yeah
<br />other than that,, wine makes all the programs i wanted to run... run,, and every ubuntu program thats x86 based works &lt;3 god ji hate arm
<br />
<br />also!!!! its been a while since my last blog post so!!! im gonna talk about my site now
<br />i made a mobile version of the site,, really cool,, i updated pik2pedia like 15 times,, i didered my first bit of javascript,, i ruined my credibility at school by directing people to a site that said i was a furry (mY website), anddd uh. images!
<br />yeah! yeah! yeah! uh! ummm uhh
<br />
<br />drawing!!!! im slowly getting better... and worse >_>
<br />like... ive been working on like actually full body pieces and generally getting a Pretty Cool Thing set up but!!!! im still like!!! getting worse at my more detailed faces that i made to like!!!! make things more diverse???? like characters can have different amounts of face tufts. but thats it
<br />
<br />annnnyways tarnsformice ! im playinging it. off and on &lt;/3 
<br />its like “oh i wanna do this thing now!!! now this thing!!!!! now this thing oh whoops its 8 i cant play transformie now :(“ and!!!!!!! its dumb why cant i just do everythign i want to give me more hours to Eat Sandwiches!!!!!!!!!!!!! grrrr

<br /> so uh. im done ! for now! i promise ill try to post more blogs &lt;/3
  
</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>

    <title> computing and stuffs !!!
    </title>
  <pubDate>1 12 2023 9:26 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
<p> heya!!!
<br /> so uh... this is kinda a follow up to “laptops and not lapdogs”,, 
<br /> ive messed around on the laptop more,, and so ive kinda gained more knowledge about its limitations and uh.. its capabilities..
<br /> ive also been doing Stupid Stuff on my pi,, so thats a thing :P 
<br />..i talked about mypal in the last blog,, but woww does it Not Like It when you have less than a gig of ram lollll
<br /> so uh... ive installed a few apps.. ive also found work arounds for [ONE] app...
<br /> so uh... im gonna talk about that lol :P 
<br />
<br /> i just had mypal and like... nothing else for the first few days.. i kinda just messed around with the programs that were already installed,, as well as getting mad at the fact that installation of office 2010 was corrupted.. 
<br />...i think i tried to uh... install firezilla,, cuz i thought you needed an ftp client to go to ftp servers... though,, you cannn actually go to it via the file browser by going to ftp://whatever the ip is... im so stewpid
<br />..uh.. i installed photoshop cs4 (the main ver. of ps i use) and it!!! actually works!!!!!! i guess it makes sense for something that released in like 2005 but. for some reason i was expecting it to just... not.. i also installed itunes because. uh. hold on let me go on a tangent</p>
<h3>some stupid person rants about itunes and cds</h3>
<p> so you know how itunes has this thing where you can uh. rip cds right
<br /> wellll if you already have the album on the computer via like the itunes store or something,, it just installs it on top of the album tracks already on your hard drive...
<br /> also!!! when you sync anything!!! it syncs the itunes version and the cd version if the cd audio is on your hard drive!!!!! even if you delete the itunes version!!!!!! and!!!!! it sucks just so much!!!!!!!!!! aaaaaaaaaaaa!!!!!!!!!!!1
</p>
<p>ok ok,, back on track...
<br /> so i installed itunes right? 
<br /> it actually doesnt eat up all of your ram so. tahts nice
<br /> i also installed fusion
<br />..i tried out gens before,, but the button config just did NOT wanna work so back to the Better Genesis Emulator in my opinion
<br /> uh.. i also tried to instal firebird 1.03 or something...
<br /> theres no password option when setting up an account so. that fell through
<br /> heh...
<br /> oh also!!!! i changed my xp vm to the workgroup on the laptop to see what that was about,, and all that happened was that
<br />- i could not do anything to the vm via the laptop
<br />- i could see the scheduled tasks and the printers from the laptop on the vm
<br />- absolutely nothing else
<br />
<br />...also,, bitview doesn't actually allow me to upload a 2 gb video yet... so my 7 minute long Roblox Playthrough will not be going up yet :[ if you even care about that hahah
<br />...
<br />
<br /> well,, i have nothing else to say... have fun Not Dying!!!!
</p>
  
</description>
</item>


<item>
    <title> sonic adventure 2 : really neat game !!!! woooo
    </title>
  <pubDate>1 9 2023 </pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
<p> heya!!!
<br /> ive been trying to move away from the uh.. daily blogs of the last few months to a more conventional style of blogging..
<br /> cuz uh.. writing blogs every day isnt too interesting when thats alllll you do 
<br /> so!! im Actually Doing Things instead of just spending all my time blogging and then blogging and then bl
<br /> ok back on track
<br />
<br /><a> sonic adventure 2!!!!</a>
<br /> i got it like.. a few days ago and uh.. here are some first impressions n stuff
<br /><a> story impressions n stuff :P </a>
<br /> i thought like.. the actual story was Pretty Cool 
<br /> like.. in the hero story your On The Lam (though you didnt taser a mime) and you still gotta stop robotnik and hes gonna blow up earth and HE BLEW UP HALF THE MOOn and you break into the president’s limo and,,,,,,,,,,,, and thats the hero story...
<br /> and uh. the animation 
<br /> compared to sa1,, its super lively and cool and.. sure that doesnt mean much but. like im comparing their last thing to their next thing and its just.. so much better.. 
<br />..the mocap stuff is kinda jank,, but its people trying to act out pre-spoken dialogue in a mascot suit..  id like to see you try that :P 
<br />but like!!!! the facial animations are great!!! sure theyre kinda delayed,, but theyre as expressive as sa1 was <em>trying</em> to be.. if sonic adventure was remastered with the same level of expressiveness and care put into the animations,, then the story would be.. better for some,, i bet.. (unfortunately, we got a half-trying half not port that just <em>kills</em> the lighting.. gah why is sadx so ugh) 
<br /><a> gameplay ‘n stuff</a>
<br /> uh.. now i get to talk about the animations in gameplay!!! WOAAAAAAAAHHHHHH
<br /> the in-game animation is so COOL sonic looks like an actual breathing organism shadow has these cool Slip Slide-y Space Shoes the mechs look and feel like mechs and uh. rouge and knuckles look Better animation-wise. yeah,
<br />
<br />..im too lazy to actually uh.. talk about each stage in-debth so im just gonna. fly through the speed stages and then talk about the mech and hunting playstyles
<br />
<br /> city escape is the best intro ever, metal harbor is COOL, green forest is COol, pyramid cave or whatever it was called is. fffffffine. crazy gadget is COol, radical highway is the intro ever (it sucks (not really i just dont like it,)) sky rail is cool, white forest is Alright, i forgot the thing after that ill add it later, and both of the hedgehog’s “final _____” are really tough,, but feel slickk to pull off !!!
<br /> ok. uh.
<br /> you know gamma’s stages,, right? its like a sonic-y take on a Gun Game without being an edgy mess of bad game design haha yeah im so cool i make jabs at the series’ low points i should get a gold star totally im such a good reviewer
<br />
<br /> anyways, take gamma’s lock on - time attack - point scoring - classic arcade mode and remove the uh. the time restriction. and make the platforming either Boring, or Way Too Hard and Dumb. yeah. theyre still fun tho :P 
<br />
<br /> and uh. you know knuckles’ thing last game? yeah make him do it again. and then make him find keys and stuff and uh. make Another New Character and give her more interesting objectives. eyah. i like rouge’s stages more
<br /> except for mad space
<br /> never ask anyone who’s played sa2 about mad space
<br /> please
<br />
<br /><a>mewzak</a> (read it like weird al said it that one time)
<br /> so uh. sonic games are known for their good soundtracks so you already know that its AAAAAAAA
<br /> i think more people have heard escape from the city then the halo theme,,,,
<br /> and like.. all of sonic’s songs are super memorable to me.. if you showed me a video of a stage with no audio i could probably imagine the music in my head,,,
<br /> knuckles’ songs are all amazing raps and i just wanna pat his head hes so silly!!!!!! hehehe!!!!
<br /> tails’ songs all use a lot of the same.. bright slap bass which is sooo heckin fitting for his theme,, but kinda make his stages feel like fun nights: out in the city!!! in the prison!!! going across the desert!!!! blehhh!!!!!!! hes got such silly tunes i love it 
<br /> shadow is uh. emo so he has emo songs but not the tally hall emo its the breakcore with distorted lyrics and harsh wavy synths emo. yeah . white forest’s theme grew on me kinda but other than that Eh.
<br /> rouge’s songs are all jazzy kinda like knuckles’ songs but. they dont have cheesy raps sang by her so they kinda fade into the background..
<br /> i dont remember any off robotnik’s songs but E.G.G.M.A.N.’s chorus has been stuck in my head sense the first day i heard it OGUH
<br />.. i have no other words for the soundtrack other than its GOOd i like it so soso much it makes me go yayay!!!!! :DDDD!!!!! :3333 XD (-- dead from yayyyyyy!!!!!
</p>  
  
</description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> laptops and not lapdogs
    </title>
  <pubDate>1 5 2023 11:11 am</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>

<p>heyos!!!
<br />a lil while ago,, as in like.. 4 days ago,, i got my mom's old windows xp laptop.. from one of my dad's friends
<br /> its got half a gig of ram,, and a intel celeron m (1.30 ghz max).. so its not the fastest thing ever..
<br /> heck,, it has trouble closing mypal.. 
<br /> but!! more ram is shiping!! and i can still uh.. use bitview on it :P
<br /> it also doesnt have wifi intergrated into it... but it has a internet card,, so it still connects to the internet '_'
<br />
<br />..i kinda just use it as a thing to download things onto while other things are busy.. i have an antivirus,, mypal (a browser),, and photoshop :P
<br /> for <em>some reason</em> i tried to install roblox on it at one point,, but xp isnt supported anymore.. so uh.. yeah im dummy
<br />
<br />..i think thats it..
<br /> seeyahs
</p> 

</description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> dreamcast? mroe like uh um funcast uh
    </title>
  <pubDate>12 31 2022 11:30 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>

<p> what a year.. what a heckin year
<br /> well,, im stuck at my grandma's so i cant really celebrate so
<br /> why not be "productive" while i have nothing else to do !!!!1!!!!
<br />
<br />..
<br /> i uh
<br />i have nothing else to talk about so im gonna talk about my experiences with the dreamcast (wow! experiencing something 12 months after you got it thats so super cool)
<br />
<br /> uh.. sonic adventure is really fun !!
<br /> so fun that uh.. ive a-ranked every level in sonic's campain up until sky deck which im working on..
<br /> also skiping casinopolis because i dont want to spend 18 minutes in total on that.. thing :(
<br />..
<br /> ive actually beaten the game,, too.. all on a crt
<br /> ive actually never beaten it before last time because i got stuck on big's story when i uh. got the steam port when i was like 11
<br />..
<br /> ive also been working on chao rasing.. because im insane and crazy and bonkers and STUPID
<br />
<br /> soul calabur is Fine Enough when your just going for all the unlockables,, and Fun when your playing with uh idk your dad
<br />
<br /> crazy taxi is a neat enough arcade port,, might help me with route planning the next time i go to the black hills.. as if thats gonna happen again :P
<br />.. also i could probebly just use the gba ver. for route planning,, but the dc version is better for at-home use i guess
<br />
<br /> and the dreamcast web browser is Neat but i cant really use it.. maybe if i set up dreamcast live someday ill like.. see if i can work on my site from my dreamcast lolll
<br />.. it might not support js though.. so i might not be able to use the web editor :P
</p>

</description>
</item>

<item>
    <title> chomebooks and pain
    </title>
  <pubDate>12 15 2022 8:30 am</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>

<p> heayah!!
<br />..i guess ill talk about some stuff about how im making this site
<br /> more specifically,, the parts you dont see.. or cant see..
<br />..im still working on this in school,, where everyone is loud and annoying anid its painful to think and goodLORD WHY IS EVERYONE SHOUTING
<br></br>
<br />..i do most of my coding in school,, where we have to use chromebooks.. so i like. use the neocitites web editor.. 
<br />..sometimes the school likes to do this Thing where they block the editor so i just. work on stuff that can be copied and pasted in a gdoc.. like basically all of these blog posts..
<br />
<br /> i usually make webpages because im like “wow!!!! i wanna show off this thing and then i spend like 50 hours making that thing and perfecting that thing..
<br />
<br />..ok time to do some science stuff in math because i dont wanna fail scienceeee 
<br /> uh. yeah
<br /> bye
</p>
    
</description>
</item>



<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> mdiscort + new album stuff!!!
    </title>
  <pubDate>12 14 2022 8:22 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
<p> ..i joined alot of discord servers to try and feel less.. lonely
<br /> one of them is like. super inactive and lame unless this one person talks and just.. makes everyone argue against him..
<br />..the other one is like super active!! and has a ton of cool people!! of course we're all Not Normal because. the server is about cool music that i like so;. yeaf
<br />
<br />..im also kinda working on a new album!! its gonna have.. 2 unnew songs,, and more than 3 new songs 
<br /> will be free to download!! gdrive though because i have no idea how to host like a site through an ftp server and also isps and actually having to use my home network and i doubt my pi could keep up and. yeah
<br /> more info will be available on xDx3xP whenever i decide on said info
<br />
<br />..i also went to get an eye exam yesterday 
<br /> i got like.. really cute frames!!! and also they wont have a broken bow!!!!!!!!!!!!!! i broke my current glasses haha ;;*
<br />
<br /> so uh.. yeah
<br /> seeya
</p>
  
</description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> mph
    </title>
  <pubDate>12 23 2022 4:50 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
<p>..hi
<br /> ive been gone because!! i manly work on this site during school actually 
<br />..my production will absolutly die in the summer..
<br />
<br /> uh.. i beat sonic 2 for the first time
<br /> as well as beating sa1 100% (storrrry wise i have not collected all of the emblems im not insaneeeeee or anything i swear) 
<br />..ive made like,, 2 songs too 
<br /> so yayayayayayayayaya why havent i done anything cool with my time
<br />
<br /> so uh.. yeah..
<br /> thats it!!!!!! ugh
</p>

</description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> aCHK
    </title>
  <pubDate>12 11 2022 12:26 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
<p> alot can happen in like. 3 months
<br /> and everytghing is a lot!!!!!!111!!!! ugh
<br />
<br /> eh
</p>


</description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> justa drink that too
    </title>
  <pubDate>12 10 2022 7:33 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  

<p> heya!!!
<br /> i cleaned up my room and uh. made jellyfloat pool better (previously thepikminever
<br /> also uhm. im a cat mewo maoew merw 
<br /> uh. too busy listening to a new album to Talk!!!! : D
</p>

</description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> it waws a snow day
    </title>
  <pubDate>12 8 2022 10:02 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
 
<p> uhh heya!!
<br></br> ive had this thing stuck in my head ever sence i started this site
<br></br> .."web pages really are pages on the web.. they just cost less"
<br></br> i havent really been able to get that thought out of my head.. its just.. something there..
<br> </br>
<br></br> OHY EAH i uhm. so far i beat pikmin 2 for the 8th time and made my blog on tumblr better.. not much else though..
<br></br>
<br></br> ..seeya
</p>
  
</description>
</item>


<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> the void you fill withf
    </title>
  <pubDate>12 7 2022 8:20 am</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
<p> heya!!
<br></br> uh. hai
<br></br> i beat TWO WHOLE CAVES in pikmin 2 yesterday isnt that neat
<br></br> uh. i beat the cavern of chaos and. hole of heroes 
<br></br> i went through hoh once with EVERYONE and once with. 80 blues 
<br></br> can you guess what the blues were for??????????/ thtats right ultra spicying the Min then just repeatedly bittering the mal so that no one died ever. yeaf
<br></br>
<br></br> i also started on da dream den yesterday!! <a href="https://thepersonever.neocities.org/pikmin/pik2wistfulwild.html"> heres what im doin to the td !!111!!! (pikmin twoeh spoilers)</a> 
<br></br>
<br></br> ..
<br></br>
<br></br> uh.. other than that i didnt do much.. 
<br></br> i guess updating stuff when i got home is cool??????? idk
<br></br> im kinda dummy hi 
<br></br>
<br></br> uh.. bye i guess
  </p>
</description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> nO ideaz :( 
    </title>
  <pubDate>12 6 2022 8:17 am</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
<p> heya!!
<br></br> i didnt sleep very well last night.. why? idk
<br></br>
<br></br> uh.. im kinda outta ideas again ;;
<br></br> so uh!! if you ever have ideas for this site!!! put em in the guestbook or chatbox!!! i wont be able to read teh chatbox until im out of school but!!!!!! dewit!!!!!! mountain dew gives you brain damage by the way im not joking
<br></br>
<br></br> oh yeaf i. beat some sand castle yesterday :> 
<br></br>
<br></br> ..
<br></br>
<br></br> seeyah
</p>
  
</description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> chuckyas and uh frogs
    </title>
  <pubDate>12 5 2022 9:16 am</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
<p> heya!!
<br></br>uh. i um
<br></br>i tried pikmin wars yesterday
<br></br> it was Stuypid and Dumb and Slightly Fun :) 
<br></br> the PIKMIN GUN section had me very confused and kinda engaged 
<br></br> every other part was Kinda Boring ! 
<br></br>
<br></br> i couldnt get past the chuckyas parttttt
<br></br>
<br></br> yeah. uh
<br></br> 
<br></br> ive played through pikmin 2 like 7 times : P 
<br> </br>
<br></br> uh. yeahf
<br></br>
<br></br> bye
</p>  

</description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> pikmin 2 for low definition displays!!!
    </title>
  <pubDate>12 2 2022 8:16 am</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>

<p> heya!!
<br></br> yesterday,, i set up all my av consoles onto my old crt
<br></br> you may be like “why?” and well..
<br></br> its because its the only 4:3 tv i have..
<br></br> so uh.. like pikmin 2 looks.. fine,, with black boarders
<br></br> stretched out it looks stretched out (ew!) and with 16:9 patches it still doesnt look the greatest..
<br></br> but on a 4:3.. it really looks like you can see everything..!!
<br></br> i know thats like.. stupid sounding,, considering you can see the most with 16:9 patches on a 16:9 display,, but just.. it looks better than you’d expect
<br></br> also we love katamari sounds funny on a mono tv :P
<br></br>
<br></br> uh..  yeah
<br></br>
<br></br> seeya?
</p>
  
</description>
</item>


<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> white ! picket fenceeesssss~
    </title>
  <pubDate>12 1 2022 8:14 am</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
 <p> heya!!
<br></br> site’s been up for a month,, huh..
<br></br> ..
<br></br>
<br></br> ive backed up a few versions to a dvd.. i might “relase” them soon haha
<br></br>
<br></br> ..
<br></br> uhh i uh. have random parts of suburbia overture stuck in my head :] 
<br></br>
<br></br> ..
<br></br> 
<br></br> seeyah
</p>
  
</description>
</item>


<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> yeah snow day 
    </title>
  <pubDate>11 30 2022 8:36 am </pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
<p>hellogh
<br></br> it was a snow day yesterday!! thats why i was lazy and did Practically Nothing
<br></br> uh. by practically nothing i mean
<br></br> - i “beat” we love katamari
<br></br> - i beat pikmin 1 NewPlayControl with the help of uh. like 43 pikmin dying to the emperor bulb ;;
<br></br>
<br></br> ..
<br></br> 
<br></br> uhhh yeah..
<br></br>
<br></br> seeyaeh
</p>  
  
</description>
</item>


<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> psytriactric supply or whatever 
    </title>
  <pubDate>11 28 2022 9:02 am</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
<p> HI HELLO HI UH WELCME TO NOt THANKSGIVING
<br></br> a lot can happen in 6 days..
<br></br> like uh
<br></br>
<br></br> - making 6 whole youtube videos i thinik
<br></br> - getting a boyfriend
<br></br>- uhh renting games from your Local Library 
<br></br> - not beating we love katamari
<br></br>
<br></br> so.. thats whats happened with me so far..
<br></br>.. 
<br></br> at least im back on web development!! thats cooler tgan me
<br></br>..
<br></br>
<br></br> yeah bye
</p>
</description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> hello again !!! -the shoulder 
    </title>
  <pubDate>11 21 2022 8:31 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
<p> heya !!!! 
<br></br> in like.. 2 days im going on thanksgiving break so expect this site’s activity to go DOWn 
<br></br> im also uh. still working on the Pikmin Secret
<br></br> but you can still find it!! so uh. go do that
<br></br>
<br></br> bye
</p> 

</description>
</item>


<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> aCHK
    </title>
  <pubDate>11 20 2022 9:05 am</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
<p> ackk i forgot to post yesterday :((((
<br></br> sorry for being so dummy stupid!! i was making videos
<br></br><br></br> 
<iframe width="450" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/4LNmP1zCEOs" title="yeah" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture"></iframe>
<br></br><br></br>
so uh..
<br></br> yeahhh
<br></br>
<br></br> seeya
</p>
  
</description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> PIKMEIND AND roleplay
    </title>
  <pubDate>11 18 2022 8:30 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
<p> heya!!
<br></br> yesterday i.. uh...
<br></br> uhhhh umm
<br></br> i uh. did rp 
<br></br> and it was like.. genuinely relaxing..
<br></br> heh..
<br></br> oh yea!! im also working on PIKMIN SUBPAge which might be a secret when i implement it so shhhhhhhhhhhhh
<br></br>
<br></br>..
<br></br>
<br></br> seeeyaeh
</p>

  
</description>
</item>


<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> stuff.. 
    </title>
  <pubDate>11 17 2022 10:33 am</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
<p> heya!!
<br></br> yesterday i uh made music basicly the whole time i was home..
<br></br> i finally relased a new track ;; 
<br></br> <a href='thepersonever.neocities.org/xdx3xp/tracks.html' target='_blank'> you can listen to it here!!!</a>
<br></br>
<br></br>.. i think i revamped random junk a few days back
<br></br> i think its a lot better now.. although yk
<br></br> you might dissagree.. haha
<br></br>
<br></br> ..
<br></br>
<br></br> fun fact: i technically implmented a loop ive had in my head in a song that never relased here
<br></br> only problem is.. its not good at all
<br></br> ..
<br></br>
<br></br> maybe someday ill remake it..
<br></br><em> someday</em>
<br></br>
<br></br> ....
<br></br>
<br></br> seeya,, i guess :P
</p>
  
</description>
</item>


<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> zoom brain useless for writing 
    </title>
  <pubDate>11 16 2022 8:18 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>

<p> heya!!
<br></br> uh.. i did stuff yesterday?? 
<br></br> yeah.. 
<br></br>
<br></br> a few website things and uh uh uh u h
<br></br> sorry my brain is VROOM 
<br></br> i cant really say anything significant right now...
<br></br>
<br></br> ..
<br></br>
<br></br> sorry 
</p>


</description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> music updates maybe?????
    </title>
  <pubDate> 11 15 2022  8:18 am</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
<p> haie !!
<br></br> im.. less tired,, i guess
<br></br> its more so out of obligation.. haha....
<br></br> school and stuff :P
<br></br>
<br></br>..
<br></br>
<br></br> i actually have a few ideas!! (woa)
<br></br> its about moving my music recommendation stuff over to the random junk subpage
<br></br> haha.. ill have to update the thumbnail of some stuff though.. 
<br></br> ..
<br></br> yeah
<br></br>
<br></br> ....
<br></br>
<br></br> i might also test out centering for this rss thing once im home
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br> i guess thats it..
<br></br> seeya !!!
</p>

  
</description>
</item>



<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> ow
    </title>
  <pubDate>11 14 2022 5:30 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
  
  <p> im too tired to do anythign sorry </p>
  
</description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title>GOLDFISH.</title>
  <pubDate>11 13 2022 4:02 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>

<p> HI I FORGOT TO MAKE A NEW ONE YESTERDAY SORRY :(((((
<br></br> ah who cares.. its not like i did much
<br></br> i saw a movie.. and i played games
<br></br> anddd that was it :P 
<br></br>
<br></br> ....
<br></br>
<br></br> i also made my pi into an always running (when on) ftp server
<br></br> because!!! gdrive stinks !!!!!!!
<br></br>
<br></br> i also found an actually good ftp app for my phone
<br></br> if you have an iphone (im insane i own apple product),, iTransfer is like.. actually adequate for free
<br></br> if you have and andriod though uh
<br></br> im kinda dummy and cant help you with that!!! haha
<br></br>
<br></br> ..
<br></br>
<br></br> im outta ideas for this site please if you wanna see something TELL ME 
</p>

    </description>
</item>



<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title>random updates that dont matter to you :P </title>
  <pubDate>11 11 2022 9:26 am</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
    
<p> heya!!!! 
<br></br> well.. im typing this on google docs,, of all things
<br></br> i even made the rss version on gdocs....
<br></br> yeah.. theres no notepad or anything similar on the school chromebook lol
<br></br> i usually browse with firefox anyways..
<br></br>
<br></br> ... 
<br></br>
<br></br> ive been kinda lightheaded recently.. 
<br></br> ..i think its because <a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XZL_9WiZVtc'> CHRISTMAS WILL BE SOON (OH OH) </a>
<br></br>..
<br></br> ive also been having more bloody noses haha
<br></br>
<br></br> ..
<br></br>
<br></br> i got through a lill bit of rhythm heaven megamix yesterday 
<br></br> by a lill,, i mean
<br></br> -i got through like one world
<br></br> -i superbed like 2 games that i got oks on my first time
<br></br> - meow!
<br></br>
<br></br> ..yeah
<br></br>
<br></br>
<br></br> seeya,, i guess 
</p>

    </description>
</item>


<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title>school stuff</title>
  <pubDate>11 10 2022 11:09 am</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>

<p> well,, im at school again..
<br></br> now im REALLY outta ideas for this site.. 
<br></br> i guess i could talk about my school in this blog..? 
<br></br> uhhhh
<br></br> ..theres a few annoying kids i guess
<br></br> and by "annoying",, i really mean "wow i dont personally like you please stop interacting with me :D" or "wow. please shush how do you talk so much"
<br></br> but theres only like.. 3 kids like that 
<br></br> most of the teachers here are like actually cool too!! so uh
<br></br> its a Cool School (tm) 
<br></br>
<br></br> uh..
<br></br>
<br></br> stuff only seen in rss time!!!!
<br></br> or something :P
<br></br>..
<br></br> im not gonna be able to test how it looks in an rss thing.. because im at school 
<br></br> so if theres anything wrong uh
<br></br>
<br></br> blame that
<br></br>
<br></br> ..
<br></br>
<br></br> fun fact: i actually convert all my blog articles to rss by hand :P
<br></br>
<br></br> its really just adding GREATERTHAN /br LESSTHAN infront of all the brs..
<br></br> its the same with all the images lol
<br></br>
<br></br>..
<br></br>
<br></br> bye i guess ;_;
</p>

    </description>
</item>


<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title>might not be sick soon!!</title>
  <pubDate>11 9 2022 7:31 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
<p> uh.. i might be not sick soon
<br></br> that would be nice!! i would like.. be able to do stuff again
<br></br> ive just been home all day.. played a few games....
<br></br> ..im gonna go add some stuff to the collection now
<br></br> sorry for the shorter letters :((
</p>

    </description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> sick..</title>
  <pubDate>11 8 2022 11:10 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>

<p><span> EUGHT CHOUGH COUGH 
<br></br> im like.. sick so my brain is
<br></br> dead, basicly
<br></br> thats why i havent really done anything.. haha
<br></br> so... yeah
<br></br> hopefully soon!!!!!! ill be able to be good and stufff
<br></br> oooogh motivationless typing soon
</span></p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title> RSS IS UP AND RUNNING!!!!</title>
  <pubDate>11 7 2022 8:15 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
<p> HEY GUYS. I MADE AN RSS FEEDDDDDDD
<br></br> your already lookin at it!!
<br></br>thats it. bye bye nowf
</p>


<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title>A TESTT</title>
  <pubDate>11 7 2022</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
      <p>this is a test :D </p>

    </description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title>sixth thing</title>
  <pubDate>nov. 6 2022</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
      <p>..just look at the weblogs :( </p>

    </description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title>fifth thing</title>
  <pubDate>nov 5,, 2022 1:19 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>

<p> heya !! 
<br></br> im kinda running outta ideas for this site.. 
<br></br> basicly everything so far has been "hey look at these pictures!! im gonna write a paragraph about all of them"
<br></br> and thats like.. boring,, right??
<br></br> so.. what should i even do next..? 
<br></br> maybe ill try to make some stuff in javascript.. maybe ill just add more iframes 
<br></br> who knows?? not me lol
<br></br> so uh.. yeah
<br></br> guess ill go make some more iframes :l
</p>

    </description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title>fourth thing</title>
  <pubDate>nov 4; 2022 6:22 pm</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
<p> so i took a walk and.. i think i found something out about how my brain works while listening to music maybe??
<br></br> like
<br></br> i kinda sway to the music..
<br></br>  <img style="height: 100px" src="https://thepersonever.nocities.org/iframes/tusexplaination.png"></img>
<br></br> so.. yea!!
<br></br> ya learn something new every day
</p>

    </description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title>third thing</title>
  <pubDate>nov 4; 2022 9:22</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
<p> heya !!
<br></br> i uhhh got overstimulated and felt dysphoric like 2 seconds ago but uh
<br></br> fine now!!
<br></br> uh.. i added my first iframe to a webpage (this one) today :P
<br></br>..i might go on a walk when i get home,, not sure though
<br></br> last night i finished up the cds page,, did some more maintenance,, and added more stuff to the homepage
<br></br> oh!! i also made the xDx3xP website thing ^^
<br></br> today im gonna work on more formatting things,, as well as actually changing page backgrounds haha
<br></br> so.. i think thats it
<br></br> sorry for getting so formaty with these blogs..
</p>

    </description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title>second thing</title>
  <pubDate>nov 3; 2022 8:33 am</pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
<p> hi again!!
<br></br> i think i conked my head last night..
<br></br> or maybe i was zoinked out??? i dont know im just. still tired :P
<br></br> uhh.... i did a lot of maintenance,, but i didnt really do anything new..
<br></br> oh yeah!! i added photoshops and collections
<br></br> also- by “maintenance” i really just mean adding content to already existing pages 
<br></br> so uh.. yeah
<br></br> not much new lol 
<br></br> oh yeah.. im also going to the dr’s office today
<br></br> theres gonna be uh needle stuff haha
<br></br>..
<br></br>
<br></br> OH YEAH theres also a secret on the music page
<br></br> see if you can find it!! ;^3
<br></br>
<br></br>
</p>

    </description>
</item>

<item>
  <guid>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</guid>
    <title>first thing</title>
  <pubDate>nov 2; 2022 8:52 AM </pubDate>
<link>https://thepersonever.neocities.org/blogg.html</link>
  <description>
        <p>  well uh.. hi
<br> im probably gonna use this blog as a more in-depth site news,, so.... yeah
<br>
<br>uhhhh 
<br>
<br>yesterday i made.. a lot
<br>it was the first day this site was up lol
<br> music suggestions.. about me.. goals..
<br> almost everything on this site
<br> in fact,, ill be listing anything thats new on this blog,, as well as the site news
<br> technically,, i dont even have the site news set up yet lol
<br>
<br>..
<br> fun fact.. i actually host most of my images offsite
<br> i havent even used 10% of my storage.. 
<br>
<br>.. oh! ive also worked on this site on 3 devices
<br> a raspberry pi,, a windows desktop (where i did most of the work) and..
<br> a chromebook
<br> because i worked on this at school
<br> im glad its unblocked ;_;</br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></br></p>

    </description>
</item>
</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>